<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1134: Reading Poetry</title>
    <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 1134: Reading Poetry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 0</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/0/</guid>
      <description>Essay 0 - &amp;ldquo;First Day&amp;rdquo; #  Due: Monday, September 7th, 22:00
Prompt #  We spent the first class reading from five poems. Pick one, re-read it and write about what you notice first (15 minutes). Then familiarize yourself with its source or supplementary materials (as noted on the slides). Take a break and do something entirely unrelated. Re-read the poem, and write about anything new you observe (30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 1</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/1/</guid>
      <description>Essay 1 - &amp;ldquo;Line&amp;rdquo; #  (Due Wednesday, 9/23, 22:00)
Prompt #  Consider the following passage from Robert Hass&amp;rsquo;s A Little Book on Form:
 The sentence imitates insight. It is the mode of individuation, the thought that separates us from others and gives us a self. To say it another way, the sentence is being, enjambment is excess of being, or being in process, reaching toward itself. Which is its basic characteristic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 2</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/2/</guid>
      <description>Essay 2 - &amp;ldquo;Ritual and Fiction&amp;rdquo; #  (Due Wednesday, 10/14, 22:00)
Prompt #  As we have discussed in class, lyric poetry may be defined in terms of its “ritual” and “fictional” elements. Choose a poem and identify specific words and lines where the “ritual” element is particularly salient, i.e. where repeated patterns occur. Then consider how the poem might be narrated as in a novel or film. Who is speaking?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 3</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/3/</guid>
      <description>Essay 3 - &amp;ldquo;Punctum&amp;rdquo; #  (Due Friday, 10/30, 22:00)
Prompt #  In Camera Lucida, Roland Barthes seeks to describe how photographs generate desire in him as a viewer, and comes up with two key terms, studium and punctum. Read his definition below:
 What I feel about these photographs derives from an average affect, almost from a certain training. I did not know a French word which might account for this kind of human interest, but I believe this word exists in Latin: it is studium, which doesn’t mean, at least not immediately, “study,” but application to a thing, taste for someone, a kind of general, enthusiastic commitment, of course, but without special acuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 4</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/4/</guid>
      <description>Essay 4 #  Design your own prompt and run it by me. A more definitive list of suggested prompts will be determined by week 8.
Suggestions #   Write a comparative essay using your own punctum and another classmate’s punctum for the same poem. Feel free to collaborate more with your classmate by asking them further questions. Write a comparative essay on two different poems of your choosing; they may be poems by the same author, from the same collection, or by different authors working in a related form or genre.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>