<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Schedule on 1134: Reading Poetry</title>
    <link>https://1134.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Schedule on 1134: Reading Poetry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 21:24:40 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://1134.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/schedule/spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/schedule/spring/</guid>
      <description>COML 1134: Reading Poetry (FWS) #  Week 1: Feb 8, 10, 12 – Introduction #  This week we will read and respond to five poems. What do you notice in each? 2/8: Introduction
Today we discuss what &#34;reading&#34; and &#34;poetry&#34; mean to you.
Be sure to complete the preliminary survey by 10 PM! Discussion Board — Introduce yourself (name, pronouns, hometown, prospective major, anything else you&amp;rsquo;d like to share) and write a brief reflection on your FWS experience last semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/fallindex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/fallindex/</guid>
      <description>Essay Horizon #  The essay sequence is designed to lead you to a final paper. Each of the assignments emphasizes a different skill, mode of argumentation, or type of writing. Here&#39;s a brief synopsis of what you should be learning by completing each essay: Essay 0: Centers observation, under few constraints. Reveals what you are accustomed to seeing in poems. The most successful essays are detailed but concise, and follow the two-step structure of the essay with fidelity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 0</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/0/</guid>
      <description>Essay 0 - &amp;ldquo;First Day&amp;rdquo; #  Due Saturday, 8/28 at 22:00
Peer review due Tuesday, 8/31 at 22:00
Prompt #  We spent the first class discussing what we mean by the word &amp;ldquo;poetic&amp;rdquo; and reading from several different poems. Your task is now to choose one of these poems and discuss how it corresponds to or wavers from your notion of the &amp;ldquo;poetic.&amp;rdquo; In order to accomplish this, please follow these steps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 1</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/1/</guid>
      <description>Essay 1 - &amp;ldquo;Rhyme, Line, Meter&amp;rdquo; #  Due Friday, 9/24 at 22:00; revisions due by 10/8 at 22:00
Prompt #   Choose a poem and think about how it employs rhyme or repetition. Take notes on what you observe. Choose a poem and think about how its lineation relates to its meaning. Is it divided into stanzas or implicit sections of a set length? How is enjambment used in the poem?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 2</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/2/</guid>
      <description>Essay 2 - &amp;ldquo;Poems in Dialogue&amp;rdquo; #  Due Friday, 10/22 at 22:00; revisions due by 11/5 at 22:00
Prompt #  As we have discussed in class, lyric poetry may be defined in terms of it use of “ritual” and “fictional” elements, in terms of the &amp;ldquo;four parameters,&amp;rdquo; or in terms of the &amp;ldquo;three voices.&amp;rdquo; These terms ultimately help us discuss the simple question: &amp;ldquo;Who is speaking, and in response to what?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 3</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/3/</guid>
      <description>Essay 3 - &amp;ldquo;Studium, Punctum&amp;rdquo; #  Due Friday, 11/29, at 22:00; revisions due by 12/1 at 22:00
Prompt #  In Camera Lucida, Roland Barthes seeks to describe how photographs generate desire in him as a viewer, and comes up with two key terms, studium and punctum. Read his definition below:
 What I feel about these photographs derives from an average affect, almost from a certain training. I did not know a French word which might account for this kind of human interest, but I believe this word exists in Latin: it is studium, which doesn’t mean, at least not immediately, “study,” but application to a thing, taste for someone, a kind of general, enthusiastic commitment, of course, but without special acuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 4</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/4/</guid>
      <description>Essay 4 - &amp;ldquo;Final&amp;rdquo; #  Due Friday, 12/10 at 22:00
Prompt #  Design your own prompt or recycle one of the previous three. You may choose to write on any poem or poet, even if you previously wrote about it. You can write an expanded version of a previous paper. The main difference between this essay and the prior ones is the length. With twice as much space, you are encouraged to do some &amp;ldquo;research,&amp;rdquo; meaning that you may write about multiple poems, connect the poems to historical background, compare the work of two different poets, connect the poems to art in another genre, or use a poetic framework not discussed in class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/archive/fall-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/archive/fall-index/</guid>
      <description>Didi Chang-Park (he)
dp625@cornell.edu
Office Hours  Welcome to Fall 2020! #  COML 1134: Reading Poetry (FWS) #  Poems are puzzles, or are they plants? In this class, we will respond to key questions like &amp;ldquo;How does this poem work?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Why do I like it?&amp;rdquo; Poems are often thought of as infinite in the possibilities of perception and wonder they produce. We will grapple with the paradox of writing about poetry in a closed, concise form without domesticating it, by investigating how reading poetry can teach us how to write anew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/archive/spring-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/archive/spring-index/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Spring 2021! Didi Chang-Park (he)
dp625@cornell.edu
Office Hours  COML 1134: Reading Poetry (FWS) #  Poems are puzzles, or are they plants? In this class, we will respond to key questions like &amp;ldquo;How does this poem work?&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Why do I like it?&amp;rdquo; We will also grapple with the paradox of writing about poetry in a closed, concise form without domesticating it, by investigating how reading poetry can teach us how to write anew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/schedule/fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/schedule/fall/</guid>
      <description>COML 1134: Reading Poetry (FWS) #  Week 1: Sept 2, 4 – Introduction #   What do you notice? ↕  9/2: Introduction
What&#39;s your relationship to reading? What does it feel like to read different kinds of texts? This week we will read five poems by A.R. Ammons, Christian Bök, H.D., Reginald Shepherd, and Juliana Spahr. What do you notice in each? 9/4: Selections from 9/2
Make the introduction post to the Discussion Board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/menu/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
