<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome! on 1134: Reading Poetry</title>
    <link>https://1134.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome! on 1134: Reading Poetry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 21:24:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://1134.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 0</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/0/</guid>
      <description>Essay 0 - &amp;ldquo;First Day&amp;rdquo; #  Due: Monday, September 7th, 22:00
Prompt #  We spent the first class reading from five poems. Pick one, re-read it and write about what you notice first (15 minutes). Then familiarize yourself with its source or supplementary materials (as noted on the slides). Take a break and do something entirely unrelated. Re-read the poem, and write about anything new you observe (30 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 1</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/1/</guid>
      <description>Essay 1 - &amp;ldquo;Line&amp;rdquo; #  Due Wednesday, 9/25, 22:00
Revisions due on 10/7, 22:00
Prompt #  Consider the following passage from Robert Hass&amp;rsquo;s A Little Book on Form:
 The sentence imitates insight. It is the mode of individuation, the thought that separates us from others and gives us a self. To say it another way, the sentence is being, enjambment is excess of being, or being in process, reaching toward itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 2</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/2/</guid>
      <description>Essay 2 - &amp;ldquo;Ritual and Fiction&amp;rdquo; #  Due Wednesday, 10/16 at 22:00,
Revisions due on 10/26 at 22:00
Prompt #  As we have discussed in class, lyric poems may be defined in terms of their “ritual” and “fictional” elements, in terms of the &amp;ldquo;four parameters,&amp;rdquo; or in terms of the &amp;ldquo;three voices.&amp;rdquo; Choose a poem (or several short ones) and demonstrate how it embodies any of these categories. You may choose to use only one of these theoretical approaches, or a blend of several.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 3</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/3/</guid>
      <description>Essay 3 - &amp;ldquo;Punctum&amp;rdquo; #  (Due Friday, 10/30, 22:00)
Prompt #  In Camera Lucida, Roland Barthes seeks to describe how photographs generate desire in him as a viewer, and comes up with two key terms, studium and punctum. Read his definition below:
 What I feel about these photographs derives from an average affect, almost from a certain training. I did not know a French word which might account for this kind of human interest, but I believe this word exists in Latin: it is studium, which doesn’t mean, at least not immediately, “study,” but application to a thing, taste for someone, a kind of general, enthusiastic commitment, of course, but without special acuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essay 4</title>
      <link>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1134.netlify.app/docs/writing/4/</guid>
      <description>Essay 4 - &amp;ldquo;Prompt&amp;rdquo; #  Draft due 11/16 or 11/30 at 22:00
Final due 12/17 at 22:00
Prompt #  Design your own prompt or recycle one of the previous three. You may choose to write on any poem or poet, even if you previously wrote about it. You can write an expanded version of a previous paper. The main difference between this essay and the prior ones is the length.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>